A Guide to the Department of Medicine Housestaff and Chief Residents Photograph Collection, 1951-2012
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Herbert E. Cushing, Chief Resident, 1986-1987, 0062_04_016; 1 Photograph B&W 8.5 x 10.25 (Box-folder 4:16)
- Brian E. Robinson, Chief Resident, 1987-1988, 0062_04_017; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:17)
- Raymond P. Smith, Chief Resident, 1987-1988, 0062_04_018; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:18)
- Nicholas W. Gemma, Chief Resident, 1988-1989, 0062_04_019; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:19)
- Walter E. Smalley Jr., Chief Resident, 1988-1989, 0062_04_020; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:20)
- Kevin P. High, Chief Resident, 1989-1990, 0062_04_021; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:21)
- Colleen A. McNamara, Chief Resident, 1989-1990, 0062_04_022; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:22)
- Raymond Brig, Chief Resident, 1990-1991, 0062_04_023; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:23)
- William V. Burgess, Chief Resident, 1990-1991, 0062_04_024; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:24)
- Brian G. Bachhuber, Chief Resident, 1991-1992, 0062_04_025; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:25)
- Matthew T. Goodman, Chief Resident, 1991-1992, 0062_04_026; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:26)
- Paul V. DeMarco, Chief Resident, 1992-1993, 0062_04_027; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:27)
- Glen L. Portwood, Chief Resident, 1992-1993, 0062_04_028; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:28)
- Paul S. Buckley, Chief Resident, 1993-1994, 0062_04_029; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:29)
- April C. Sempien, Chief Resident, 1993-1994, 0062_04_030; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:30)
- Anthony Marano, Chief Resident, 1994-1995, 0062_04_031; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:31)
- Gregory R. Weidner, Chief Resident, 1994-1995, 0062_04_032; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:32)
- William H. Maynard, Chief Resident, 1995-1996, 0062_04_033; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:33)
- Christina W. Prillaman, Chief Resident, 1995-1996, 0062_04_034; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:34)
- Margaret R. Reitmeyer, Chief Resident, 1996-1997, 0062_04_035; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:35)
- Scott A. Robinson, Chief Resident, 1996-1997, 0062_04_036; 1 Photograph B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 4:36)
- Thomas R. Gehrig, Chief Resident, 1997-1998, 0062_04_037; 1 Photograph B&W 8.5 x 10.5 (Box-folder 4:37)
- Christopher A. Klipstein, Chief Resident, 1997-1998, 0062_04_038; 1 Photograph B&W 8.5 x 10.5 (Box-folder 4:38)
- J. Murray Estess, Chief Resident, 1998-1999, 0062_04_039; 1 Photograph B&W 8.5 x 10.5 (Box-folder 4:39)
- Richard M. Ingram, Chief Resident, 1998-1999, 0062_04_040; 1 Photograph B&W 8.5 x 10.5 (Box-folder 4:40)